♪ The Big Bang Theory 9x04 ♪
Ihe 2003 Approximation
Original Air Date on October 12,
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Thank you for letting
me come speak with you.
(Bernadette:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)As my relationships
with Penny and Amy
(Sheldon:)are currently strained,
I'm turning to you
(Sheldon:)for female comfort
and encouragement.
Aww.
I'm honored.
I tried
(Sheldon:)reaching out to my mother,
but she was in Bible study.
(Sheldon:)Leonard's mother
is on a book tour.
(Sheldon:)My Mee-Maw was taking a nap,
(Sheldon:)and after a while Siri
started repeating her answers.
(Bernadette:)So, I'm your seventh choice.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I know, top ten,
pretty exciting.
(Bernadette:)How can I help you?
(Sheldon:)Well, in addition
to Amy leaving me,
(Sheldon:)Leonard's moving in with Penny.
(Sheldon:)It's difficult
not to feel abandoned.
(Bernadette:)Well, why don't you look at this
as an opportunity?
(Bernadette:)You had other roommates
before Leonard.
(Bernadette:)Maybe this is a chance
(Bernadette:)to find someone new.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I could find someone
better than Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Someone I can rub in his face.
(Sheldon:)Chris Pratt's
all the rage right now.